Guide to the Sam Kindrick Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- Photographs, 1975-2018; 1975-2010
  - Action Magazine Photographs, 1975-2018
    - Moonlight Delight (6 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Morales, Sisters (6 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Morgan, Claude [Buckboard Bookie Boys] (10 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Morning (20 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Murphy, Matt (4 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Murphy, Michael Martin (5 photographs, clipping) (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Myth (7 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Artists N-O (23 photographs) including Janice Newton, O.D. O'Doyd, Jack Orbin, Osborne Brothers, Will Owen-Gage & Jay Boy Adams (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Nell, Mary (6 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Nelson, Tracy (2 photographs) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Nelson, Willie [1 of 2] (45 photographs, negatives), includes Bobby Bare, Emmy Lou Harris, Ira Nelson (father), Ernest Tubb, Luckenbach (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Nelson, Willie [2 of 2] (39 photographs), includes Dyan Cannon, Ray Wylie Hubbard, Kris Kristofferson, Leon Russell, Specht's Store crowd, Johnny Rodriguez, Sam Kindrick (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Nelson, Willie – Family (43 photographs) including: Ira Nelson (3; 1 with Jubal Clark), Paul English (13; 1 with Emmy Lou Harris), Bee Spears (3), Bobby Nelson (4), Mickey Raphael (6), Jody Payne (4 photographs) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Nelson, Willie – Press Releases (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - New Riders of the Purple Sage (3 photographs, press release) (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Nobuko (3 photographs, negatives) (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Non Workers Union (8 photographs) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Norris, Ted "Dr. Feelgood" (6 photographs) (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Nunn, Gary P. (3 photographs) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Oak Ridge Boys (2 photographs) (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Odetta (1 photographs) (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Olson, Luke (7 photographs) (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Omar and the Howlers (13 photographs, press release, 45 RPM record: "Hoy! Hoy! Hoy! / How Do You Feel?" (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Overload (7 photographs, press release) (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Ozuna, Sunny (2 photographs) (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Artists - P (39 photographs), includes Shawn Phillips, Sunny Planto, Pointer Sisters, Pinetop Perkins (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Parton, Dolly (6 photographs, press release) (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Paycheck, Johnny (5 photographs, negatives) (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Perez, Henry (9 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Phillips, Johnny (6 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Pierce, Conrad (5 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Politicians (28 photographs) including Sherriff Bobby Kinser, Fred Semaan (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Potters Wheel (2 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Preservation Hall Jazz Band (6 photographs, press packet) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Presley, Rick (8 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Preston, Leroy (6 photographs, press packet) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Price, Ray (2 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Pride, Charley (2 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Pure Prairie League (3 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Artists Q-R (72 photographs) including Quest, The Reach, Della Reese, Todd Roberts, Ro-Tel and the Hot Potatoes, Peter Rowan, Tracy Ryan, Shake Russell, Slim Roberts (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Ramsey, Willis Alan (3 photographs, Lone Star Beer promotional) (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Randolph, Boots "Mr. Sax" (3 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Ray, Paul (3 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Reed, Jerry (1 photograph, negatives, clippings) (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Revival Brothers (2 photographs, 45 RPM "When the Night Comes / Tooth" (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Rick & Company (3 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Rico, Tony (2 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Road Apple (3 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Robbins, Marty (3 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Rodarte, Frank (11 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Rodriguez, Johnny (15 photographs, press releases) (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Rohan, Bob (3 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Rose, Ron and Friends (19 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Roxanne (6 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Rubikon (5 photographs) (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Russell, Leon (12 photographs, negatives, press release) including Sam Kindrick (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Artists - S (84 photographs) including Ravi Shankar, She & Him, Southern Ridge, Dan Staedler, Rod Stewart & Ron Wood, Ralph Straub, John Stuckey, Mike Sanders (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Sahm, Doug (3; 1 including Augie Meyers), Shawn (3) and Shandon (5) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - St. Elmo's Fire (5 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Salinas, Tony (6 photographs, negatives) (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Saluté (3 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - San Antonio Playboys [Bill Shore] (10 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Sandcastle Band (8 photographs, negatives) (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Scott, Kirk (6 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Seely, Jeanie (3 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Selena (1 photograph, signed) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Self-propelled Group (2 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Shaughnessy, Ed (3 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Shaver, Billy Joe (13 photographs), includes son Eddie Shaver (1) (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Silver City Saddle Tramps (2 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Silver Cobra (4 photographs, negatives), Karate (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Since Amelia (9 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Skizzy and the Skidmarks (3 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Sky, Ernie [Mother of Pearl] (4 photographs, press release) (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Sleepy Bear (3 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Smith Brothers Band (6 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Darden (1 photograph, press packet) (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Red (4 photographs), includes Kindrick (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Smith, Sammi (2 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Snapshot (11 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Sojourn (21 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - South Paw Tattoo (4 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Spacek, Jimmy (25 photographs) (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Spillman, Ron (4 photographs) includes Moe Bandy (1) (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Sports (47 photographs) includes pool, boxing, cars, horses (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Stagebrush (8 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Stampley, Joe (7 photographs) includes Moe Bandy (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Star Crost (7 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Star Dust (31 photographs, negatives) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Steagall, Red (17 photographs, negatives, press packet) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Steppenwolf (3 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Stewart, Gary (13 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Stevenson, B. W. (7 photographs, negatives, Lone Star Beer promotion, clipping) (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Stingrays (5 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Strait, George (5 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Strippers & Dancers (57 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Sturchio, Ditto (4 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Sylvia (9 photographs, negatives) (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Artists - T (69 photographs) including Rudy Tee, Texas Gold, B. J. Thomas, Trinidad Pan Masters, Rob Trower, Conway Twitty, Two's Company (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Taylor, Larry Joe (2 photographs), includes Gary P. Nunn (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Tchoupitoulas (9 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Tears of Joy (9 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Texas Exes (4 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Texas Top Hands [Ray Sepanik] (12 photographs, press packet) (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Theatre & Actors (11 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Thomas, Joe (6 photographs) (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Thompson, Hank (4 photographs, press envelope) (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Thornton, T. Gosney (4 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Tibbs, Casey (5 photographs), Rodeo (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Tillis, Mel (4 photographs, clippings) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Tillman, Floyd (7 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Tiny Tim (5 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Toby, Beau (2 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Torres, Patsy (5 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Trevino, Geronimo (7 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Tucker, Tanya (5 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Tubb, Ernest (14 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Two Hoots and a Holler (3 photographs, clippings) (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Artists U-Z (76 photographs) including Valentino, Townes Van Zandt, Lolita Villa, Jerry Waddel, Porter Wagoner, War, Jacky Ward, Don Williams, Edgar Winter Group, The Worx, Tom Wright, Tammy Wynette, Frank Zappa (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Uranium Savages (3 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - V, Ruben (15 photographs, CD) (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Vance, Vince [and the Valients] (24 photographs, negatives) (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Vaughan, Jimmy [Fabulous Thunderbirds] (2 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Vito and the Kactus Kickers (3 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Walker, Jerry Jeff (23 photographs) including Susan Walker, Sam Kindrick (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Warner, Ronnie [Turning Point] (4 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Watson, Dale (7 photographs, CD) (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - West, Shelly (2 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Wheat Straw (4 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Wier, Rusty (14 photographs, Lone Star Beer Promotion, clippings) (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Williams, Hank Jr. (10 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Williams, Leona (1 photograph, press release) (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Wills, Chill (2 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Wilson, Wayne [Blood Brothers] (7 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Wolfman Jack (4 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Writers (3 photographs) includes John T. Davis, Peter Gent (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Unidentified (16 photographs) (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Sam Kindrick Personal Photographs
    - Family (19 photographs), 1975-2010 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Early photographs (17 photographs), 1975-2010 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Portraits (33 photographs), 1975-2010 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Sam Kindrick – Photographs (31 photographs), 1975-2010 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Sam Kindrick – Snapshots (45 photographs), 1975-2010 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Sam Kindrick with Others – Photographs (21 photographs), 1975-2010 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Sam Kindrick with Others – Snapshots (45 photographs), 1975-2010 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Photographs without Kindrick (23 photographs), 1975-2010 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Dogs (29 photographs), 1975-2010 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Construction (41 photographs), 1975-2010 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Sam Kindrick Personal Papers, 1968-1995, undated
  The bulk of Kindrick's personal papers include clippings of his "Offbeat" column that appeared in the San Antonio Express News, 1968-1974. The column is a precursor to the workhe would later do at Action Magazine, and the subjects are similar: music, culture, off-beat stories of sports, politics, and society.
  - Cards and Letters. 2 greeting cards, blank cards, undated letter to "Jack" (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Writings By Kindrick, undated
    - Amazing Biography of Evangalist George W. Cooper (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Best of Sam Kindrick: the secret life and hard times of a cedar chopper (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - "Kindrick's Hillbilly Dictionary" (1 page, typescript) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Offbeat Column Clippings, San Antonio Express News, 1968-1974
    - September 14 – December 30, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - January 3 – June 30, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - January 1 – June 20, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - July 6 – December 31, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - January 1 – April 29, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - May 1 – August 31, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - June 1 – August 31, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - September 1 – December 30, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - January 1 – April 30, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - May 1 – July 28, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - August 13 – December 31, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - January 1 – March 30, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - April 1 – June 21, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Writings about Kindrick, 1989
    - Newspaper clippings and bail bond form for drug possession, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Writings by Burt Wyatt, 1995, undated
    - "A Story of Seven Hundred Springs" (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - "Telegraph Post Office and General Store", 1995 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials, 1983, undated
    - Business cards (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Design for a Sam Kindrick logo, MW Barcus Studios (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Flyers for Sam Kindrick's First Outdoor Revival and Music Extravaganza featuring "The Lost Gonzo Band", Sunday, June 5, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Menudo Cook-off, 1973-1974
    - Bumper stickers (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper clipping (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Letter from George Coleman, May 19, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Flyers for cookoff "starring Willie Nelson, "El Curro" & Los Flamencos, July 27-28, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Action Magazine Records, 1975-2018
  These series relates to Action Magazine itself and includes some artist press releases, advertising files, some layout pages, a wire newspaper stand, and a near-complete run of the newspaper from 1975-2018
  - Artist Press Releases, 1978-1980, undated
    - Jutebox, Volume 1, January-February (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - AC/DC, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Blue Oyster Cult (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Capps, Mark and Ray, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Cornelius, Helen (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Def Leppard (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - The Erector Set (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Kristofferson, Kris and Rita Coolidge (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Nazareth (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Pilgrimage Band, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Van Halen, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - The Who, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Action Magazine Advertising (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Oversized Items
  This series contains the oversized material in the collection, including photographs, layout designs, and broadsides.
  - Oversized Photographs: Sam Kindrick portrait (2) and Sam Kindrick with unidentified woman (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Layout design for 3 Action Magazine covers: "Chat the Cat" (September, 1980); Drug Store Cowboys (January 1981); Sir Douglas Quintet (May 1981) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - San Antonio Light, featuring "The Slings and Arrows of Outrageous Sam Kindrick", January 16, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Willie Nelson's 4th of July Picnic broadsides from Dripping Springs and College Station [both worn; College Station poster torn in several places], 1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Original pen and ink drawing of drug user behind bars. Inscribed on back to Sam, "…I went with some sick-puppy art depicting the evils of drugs – behind bars, death, etc." (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Action Magazine Issues, 1975-2018
  This series contains a near-complete run of the newspaper from 1975-2018.
  - 1975 Issues
    - Willie Nelson cover (3), March, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Jerry Jeff Walker cover (2), April, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Ben Dorsey cover (2), May, 1975 (Box 21)
    - B. W. Stephenson cover (3), June, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Leon Russell, Kinky Friedman cover (2), July, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Willie Nelson Picnic, Gina Bon Bon cover (2), August, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Ray Wylie Hubbard, Freddie King, Charlie Daniels, Rod Steward, Ron Wood cover (2), September, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Ira Nelson (Willie's father), Navajo silversmiths cover (2), October, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Kinky Friedman, David Allen Coe cover (2), November, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Sam Kindrick cover (2), December, 1975 (Box 21)
  - 1976 Issues
    - Dr. Hook and the Medicine Show cover (2), January, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Johnny Rodriguez cover (2), February, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Lawsuit against Armadillo Productions cover (2), March, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Ernest Tubb cover (3), April, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Leon Russell cover (2), May, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Willie Nelson Picnic cover (2), June, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Hank Williams, Jr cover (2), July, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Doug Sahm cover (2), August, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Fred Semaan cover, September, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Hondo Crouch death cover (2), October, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Wolfman Jack cover (2), November, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Kindrick cartoon by Bob Rohan cover (2), December, 1976 (Box 22)
  - 1977 Issues
    - Augie Meyers cover (3), January, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Dolly Parton cover, February, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Gatemouth Brown cover (2), March, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Johnny Rodriguez Telethon (with Willie Nelson) on cover (2), April, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Alex Harvey cover (2), May, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Kindrick as preacher on cover (2), June, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Skinny Pierce cover (3), July, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Amazing Brother Bob cover; ad for Lone Star Texas Music Specials, Luckenbach, on back cover, August, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Darrell McCall cover (3), September, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Esteban Jordan cover, October, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Moe Bandy cover, November, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Minnesota Fats cover, December, 1977 (Box 23)
  - 1978 Issues
    - June Carter and Johnny Cash cover, January, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Wild Tchoupitoulas cover, February, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Guich Koock cover, March, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Betty Hansen and Jody film cover, April, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Vince Vance and the Valiants cover, May, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Intergalactic chicken races at Great Worlds's Fair cover (2), June, 1978 (Box 24)
    - "Great World's Fight," Bobby Thomas and Johnny Hernandez cover, July, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Cheryl Saville cover, August, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Floyd Tillman cover, September, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Sonny Baermann's painting of Willie Nelson's guitar Trigger cover, October, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Sammy Ayala cover, November, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Action Magazine staff cover (2), December, 1978 (Box 24)
  - 1979 Issues
    - Michael Murphy cover (2), March, 1979 (Box 24)
    - "Second generation" issue; Steve Jordan, Shaun Sahm, Clay Meyers, David Montgomery-Razz, April, 1979 (Box 24)
    - Larry Franklin cover, May, 1979 (Box 24)
    - Willie Nelson Picnic cover, July, 1979 (Box 24)
    - Walter W. McAllister, Sr. "Mayor Mac" cover, September, 1979 (Box 24)
    - Paul English cover, October, 1979 (Box 24)
    - Willie Nelson cover, November, 1979 (Box 24)
    - "Tony the Mex" cover, December, 1979 (Box 24)
  - 1980 Issues
    - 6th Anniversary Issue cover, April, 1980 (Box 25)
    - Sammy Jones (pool player) cover, June, 1980 (Box 25)
  - 1981 Issues
    - Texas Top Hands cover, September, 1981 (Box 25)
    - Amelia Garza cover, December, 1981 (Box 25)
  - 1983 Issues
    - Jackie King cover, September, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Chilympiad (cover only), October, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Texas Turkey Awards cover, November, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Johnny Phillips cover, December, 1983 (Box 25)
  - 1984 Issues
    - Christian Allen "The Flash" Grimm cover (cover year is misprinted as 1983), January, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Texas Ranger Joaquin Jackson cover (2), February, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Professional football in San Antonio cover, March, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Drunks Against Mad Mothers cover, May, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Gary Stewart cover, July, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Patsy Torres cover, September, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Texas Turkey Awards cover, November, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Christmas cover, December, 1984 (Box 25)
  - 1985 Issues
    - 2 for 1 drink ban cover, January, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Johnny Rodriguez cover, February, 1985 (Box 25)
    - 10th Anniversary cover, March, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Blues: Alan Haynes, Matt Murphy, John Lee Hooker, Jimmy Spacek, April, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Tony Rico cover, May, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Erwin Heimer (blacksmith) cover, June, 1985 (Box 25)
    - D.J. Rob Houston cover (2), July, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Billy Joe Shaver cover, August, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Vietnam Vets motorcyclist cover, September, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Ray Wylie Hubbard cover, October, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Texas Turkey Awards cover, November, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Malcolm Bell cover (2), December, 1985 (Box 25)
  - 1986 Issues
    - Asa Lee Crow III cover, January, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Red Smith in memoriam cover, February, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Claude Morgan cover, March, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Bunny Eckert cover, April, 1986 (cover lists March 1986) (Box 25)
    - Fire at Action Magazine cover, May, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Jerry Jeff Walker cover, June, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Igo Mendoza cover, July, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Omar Dykes (Omar and the Howlers) cover, August, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Mack Abernathy cover (2), September, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Joe Reed (stuntman) cover, October, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Texas Turkey Awards cover, November, 1986 (Box 25)
  - 1987 Issues
    - Hector Saldaña (Krayolas) cover, January, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Hawkeye Henson (bronc rider) cover, February, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Rene Ornelas cover, March, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Henry Perez cover, April, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Jimmy Spacek cover, May, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Olly Otten cover, June, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Bob Williams cover, July, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Doc Ben Parker cover, August, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Augie Meyers cover, September, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Lonnie Brooks cover, October, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Roxanne Krezdorn cover, November, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Eric Marley cover, December, 1987 (Box 25)
  - 1988 Issues
    - Anti-fur controversy cover, January, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Pat Halpen cover, February, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Jimmie Court (Jimmie Rodgers' grandson) cover, March, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Bob Brozman cover, April, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Chris Holzhaus cover, May, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Media Awards cover, July, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Fred Allen Smith cover, August, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Kim Wong and his Trinidad Panmasters cover, September, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Victor Lopez and the Los Keys cover, October, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Texas Turkey Awards cover, November, 1988 (Box 26)
    - Darrell McCall cover, December, 1988 (Box 26)
  - 1989 Issues
    - Steve Fromholz cover, January-February, 1989. (Box 26)
    - Angela Jackson cover, March, 1989 (Box 26)
    - Paul Thompson cover, July, 1989 (Box 26)
  - 1990 Issues
    - Geronimo cover (4), September, 1990 (Box 26)
  - 1991 Issues
    - Detoxification by Acupuncture cover, November, 1991 (Box 26)
    - Hank Thompson cover, December, 1991 (Box 26)
  - 1992 Issues
    - Gary Stewart cover, April, 1992 (Box 26)
  - 1993 Issues
    - Buffalo Bill Koehne cover, January, 1993 (Box 26)
    - Erotic Poetry Valentines Festival cover, March, 1993 (Box 26)
    - Dusty Britches cover, April, 1993 (Box 26)
    - Candye Kane cover, December, 1993 (Box 26)
  - 1994 Issues
    - Paul Kozak cover, July, 1994 (Box 26)
  - 1995 Issues
    - Lu Ann Barton cover, January, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Wayne "The Train" Hancock cover, February, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Snake Boy Johnson cover, March, 1995 (Box 26)
    - 20 Year Anniversary of Action, 1975-1995 (2), April, 1995 (Box 26)
    - John Goodno, July, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Mark Gottsacker, Kevin Geil cover, August, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Mickey Mantle cover, September, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Gary Stewart cover (2), October, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Ray Benson cover (2), November, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Billie Joe Shaver cover, December, 1995 (Box 26)
  - 1996 Issues
    - Belinda Boo cover, January, 1996 (Box 26)
    - Valentines cover, February, 1996 (Box 26)
    - Country Ted Lacey cover, March, 1996 (Box 26)
    - Katherine Dawn cover, April, 1996 (Box 26)
    - Steve Owens cover, May, 1996 (Box 26)
    - Augie Meyers wedding cover (2), June, 1996 (Box 26)
    - Texacala Jones cover, July, 1996 (Box 26)
    - Danny Cowan, Neal (Dogman) Black cover, August, 1996 (Box 26)